Guide to the National Coalition for Haitian Rights Records, 1964-2020, bulk 1982-2004 RL.11314
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1986-2000, undated; bulk 1988-2000; 7; 12 boxes
  - Photographs, 1987-2000, undated; 24; 7 boxes
    - Unidentified Office/Room, undated; 5 8in. x 10in. Black-and-white (Box 159)
    - US Navy Ship Tortuga, undated; 20 4in. x 6in. Color (Box 159)
    - Violence, Deportations Of Haitians In The Batey, 1995; 18 6in. x 4in. Color (Box 159)
  - Cassettes, 1988-1998; 25; 5 boxes
    Collection contains fragile audiovisual formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
    - 32 VHS tapes, 1993-1995 (Box 160)
      VHS tapes include some commerical productions, footage of NCHR press conference, videos by other organizations dealing with events in Haiti or with Haitian-American related issues.
    - 10 VHS tapes, 72 audio-cassette tapes, 1 CD, 1 DVD, 1988-1989 (Box 161)
      VHS tapes and DVD include news shows covering AIDS/HIV; audio cassettes include recordings of conferences, meetings, press conferences and interviews, and testimonies
    - 47 audio-cassette tapes, 1 CD, 1992-1996 (Box 162)
      interviews, radio spots, testimony from immigrants
    - 24 VHS tapes, 2 audio-cassette tapes, 1990-1994 (Box 163)
      TV spots, conferences, interviews about Haiti, NCHR staff, immigrants
    - 27 VHS tapes, 1990-1998 (Box 164)
      NCHR events, short videos, productions by UN, NGO's about Haiti, refugees, immigration